const question_bank =[
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'The Firefox browser logo is not a fox? It is actually a type of species which are protected in Asia.',
        options: ['Slow Loris','Red Panda','Giant Panda'],
        correctAnswer: 'Red Panda'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'The first apple logo was featured by the famous physicist sitting under an apple tree?',
        options: ['Galileo Galilei','Isaac Newton','Albert Einstein'],
        correctAnswer: 'Isaac Newton'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'The average computer user blinks only _____ times per minute, while the normal rate is 20 times per minute.',
        options: ['7','2','10'],
        correctAnswer: '7'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'The “Google” name was created mistakenly. The original name was supposedly.,',
        options: ['Googel','Googolplex','Googol'],
        correctAnswer: 'Googol'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'This font from Microsoft was a controversial font after the 9/11 attacks in 2001 where the first plane was first to hit.',
        options: ['Arial Narrow','Lucida Console','Wingdings'],
        correctAnswer: 'Wingdings'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'The first VCR or Video Camera Recorder in the year 1956 was the size of a:',
        options: ['Piano','Television','Radio'],
        correctAnswer: 'Piano'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'That _____ of people try to plug their USB devices upside down?',
        options: ['86%','50%','30%'],
        correctAnswer: '86%'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'The first American alarm clock that was invented could only ring at ____?',
        options: ['4am','6am','12pm'],
        correctAnswer: '4am'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'The first world computer mouse was made of:',
        options: ['Metal','Wood','Chrome'],
        correctAnswer: 'Wood'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'The Astronauts of Apollo 11 couldn’t get life insurance because it cost a fortune? Instead, they signed:',
        options: ['Autographs','Waiver','Farewell Letter'],
        correctAnswer: 'Autographs'
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What was the app Snapchat originally named when launched in 2011?',
        options: ['Facesnap','Picaboo','Chatsnap'],
        correctAnswer: 'Picaboo'
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: '_____ of people type their word or sentence on google, just to see if they spelled it right?',
        options: ['10%','50%','97%'],
        correctAnswer: '97%'
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What does the word “Android” mean?',
        options: ['A green robot.','A robot with human appearance.','An articulated robot.'],
        correctAnswer: 'A robot with human appearance.'
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'What is the most used password despite all warnings is?',
        options: ['123456','abcdef','abc123'],
        correctAnswer: '123456'
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Name the syndrome in which one thinks that their phone is vibrating but isn’t?',
        options: ['Forced Vibration','Phantom Vibration','Damped Vibration'],
        correctAnswer: 'Phantom Vibration'
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: 'Fear of technology is called ________.',
        options: ['Glossophobia','Tripophobia','Technophobia'],
        correctAnswer: 'Technophobia'
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: 'What is the first name of the famous character in video game Super Mario?',
        options: ['Jumperman','Superjump','Jumpman'],
        correctAnswer: 'Jumpman'
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: 'Which combination of keyboard shortcut keys are to open Windows Task Manager?',
        options: ['Ctrl + Shift + Esc','Ctrl + Alt + Del','Ctrl + Alt + F3'],
        correctAnswer: 'Ctrl + Shift + Esc'
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: 'What is the name of the first ever video game that was released in the year 1972?',
        options: ['Super Mario','Pong','Solitaire'],
        correctAnswer: 'Pong'
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: 'What does the "M" in MP3 stand for?',
        options: ['Movie','Music','Moving'],
        correctAnswer: 'Moving'
    }
];


